I know you're excited to run the app. And I'm going to show you how to do it
without a physical device, because we'll be using the emulator. But
first, we need to install one more component from the Android SDK Manager.
Click on this button to open up the Android SDK Manager. Scroll to the bottom of
the list to find HAXM. It stands for hardware accelerated execution manager. And
it will speed up our emulator. So go ahead and deselect the other packages, and
just install this one. Accept the license, and
then continue. We have to do one more step after this to install HAXM.
I'll show you the remaining steps on a Mac, but for the other platforms you can
check the link below. First, find Android Studio under the applications folder,
and then hit show package contents. Then, in the SDK folder,
there'll be an extras folder containing an Intel folder with the HAXM folder.
Then, we click on the DMG file, open it up and
then continue. Step through this installer, and the default values are fine.
Once installation is complete, you can close all the windows.